DALLAS HILL

2/90 Oxford Street, Bulimba, QLD 4171

M: 0431 536 799 E: dallas-hill@hotmail.com

PROVEN ABILITIES IN:

- Management and staff control, decision making and leadership
- Recruitment & Termination
- Inventory control and general customer service
- Multiple Office Suites, Adobe Photoshop, 3ds Max, Revit, .bash, basic ruby
- Fluent in Apple device technical practices
- High volume data entry
- Programming of POS systems
- Craft Beer knowledge
- General bar knowledge
- Keg cleaning
- Social Media

CAREER ACCOMPLISHMENTS:

Management & Administration - I have spent most of my career in hospitality management, taking charge of large teams, writing rosters, reconciling accounts, running events and creating menus. I was also in charge of ordering stock and during my time in the brewing industry I also took part of external sales as well as reconciling accounts with bars and cafes.

Tech - Most recently, I have been working as a technical advisor for Concentrix. I ran technical support for a range of computing and mobile devices, with my skills mostly lying in iOS and macOS. I used CRM software on a daily basis as well as a range of tools to help support customers in need of technical support. I am also currently enrolled in the GenTech BootCamp course at Coder Academy.

Social Media - I have established a Facebook group, well known in the Craft Beer Community called the Brisbane Beer Barons. We currently have over 6.5K members and have bi-annual events celebrating accomplishments in the industry as well as seeking new up and coming gypsy brewers looking to make a name for themselves via our most popular annual event "Tipsy with the Gypsy".

I am also Admin to multiple Facebook pages including Baron von Brewing, one of the aforementioned Gypsy brewing companies and Stones Ginger Beer an independently owned business based in Stones Corner.

Retail - I have worked in retail for approximately 5 years in total and in that time I have managed multiple Liquor outlets, most accomplished is Hawthorne Cellars, which was acquired by the Voss Group and together with one of my colleagues was built into what is now one of Brisbane's most well-known Craft Beer Bottle shops.



QUALIFICATIONS:

- Studying Software Development at Coder Academy Current
- SBIT Revit Essentials Aug 2014 Nov 2014
- Current RSA (Responsible Service of Alcohol)
- Current RMLV (Responsible Management of Licensed Venues)
- Qualified Hairdresser Jan 2003- Dec 2006
- Balmoral State High School, Morningside Jan 2000-Dec 2004

INTERESTS:

- Software Development
- Banner & Poster design
- Social Media
- Craft Beer
- 3D Modelling
- Video Games

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

Concentrix July 2018- July 2019

Tier 2 Tech Support Specialist – Avalon Account

Brisbane Brewing Co .Nov 2016- July 2018

Operations Manager

Barcadia Kitchen & Bar Oct 2015- November 2016

Venue Manager

Hawthorne/Greenslopes Cellars Jan 2015- Oct 2015

Store Manager

Tomahawk/Tippler's Tap Mar 2014- Mar 2015

Bar Manager

Belgian Beer Café Brussels Dec 2010- Dec 2014

Operations Manager

Cloudland, Fortitude Valley June 2009-Jan 2010

Bar Manager

KG Bar, Sebel and Citigate Hotel, Brisbane CBD Jan 2009-June 2009

Bar Manager

SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE

MANAGEMENT – including Human Resources

- Management duties in recruitment and termination in my position with Barcadia Kitchen & Bar
- Taking charge of large teams through my positions with Brisbane Brewing Co. and Belgian Beer Cafe
- Balancing registers and safe on a daily basis

CUSTOMER SERVICE/STAKEOLDER LIAISON, MARKETING AND COMMUNICATIONS

- Communication between multiple tech vendors while at Concentrix
- Manage a high volume of inbound and outbound calls from existing customers
- Consistently provide superior customer service experiences for clients
- Constant communication with Engineering team
- Set and manage customer expectations
- Demonstrated ability to go above and beyond for customers
- Average of 90% positive survey return
- Willingness to apply feedback and coaching to achieve targets and expectations

TECHNICAL, ADMINISTRATION and FINANCIAL MANAGEMENT

- Supporting a wide variety of software practices across both mobile devices and computers
- Troubleshooting software issues on back end a well as end user
- bash scripting
- Data Entry
- Demonstrated ability to effectively solve problems
- Ability to manage a variety of tasks in a fast-paced environment
- Maintaining a solid cost of goods for liquor and wages
- General office administration
- General day to day Data Entry for Concentrix & Engineering
- Purchasing and stock control
- Programming of H&L system
- Designing menus and flyers for promotional purposes
- Frequent use of Microsoft Office suite

VARIOUS OTHER SKILLS

- Cleaning Kegs
- Kegging beer
- Dumping Yeast from fermenters, biofining, tank transfers & dry-hopping.
- Milling & mashing
- Cleaning Mash tun & kettle
- CIP

REFEREES:

- Mr. Isaac Mann
 Team leader Avalon Account
 Concentrix 288 Edward St. Brisbane, QLD 4000
 0405 418 432
- Miss Krista Skinner
 Team leader Avalon Account
 Concentrix 288 Edward St. Brisbane, QLD 4000
 0447 013 928
- Mr. Brendan Chan
 Head Brewer
 Brisbane Brewing Co. 124 Boundary St. Brisbane, QLD 4101
 0405 418 432
- Mr. Samuel Stewart
 Venue Manager
 Brisbane Brewing Co. 124 Boundary St. Brisbane, QLD 4101
 0400 786 757
- Mr. Samuel Carroll
 Operations Manager Hawthorne/Greenslopes Cellars
 286, Hawthorne Road, Hawthorne, QLD 4171
 0423 613 140
- Mr. Samuel Bain
 Business Owner
 Toby's Estate Albert Street, Brisbane, QLD 4006
 0421 763 762